Toni Morrison Papers, 1957-: Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
- Series 2: Correspondence, 1953-2015; 35 boxes (2 partial)
  - Tan, Amy, 1991-1995; 1 folder (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Taylor, Clyde, 1977-2004; 1 folder (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Taylor, Joseph, 1994; 1 folder (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Taylor, Susan, 1987-1995; 1 folder (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Thelwell, Ekwueme Michael, 1992-2000; 1 folder (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Theroux, Alexander, 2004-2011; 1 folder (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Thomas, Marlo and Phil Donohue, 2002-2005; 1 folder (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - Thompson, Anne E., circa 1989-2005; 1 folder (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - Tilghman, Shirley, 2006-2008; 1 folder (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - Tomlin, Lily, 2001; 1 folder (Box 95, Folder 16)
  - Traylor, Eleanor, 1999-2001; 1 folder (Box 95, Folder 17)
  - Treuer, David, 1992-2015; 1 folder (Box 95, Folder 18)
  - Treuer, Robert, 1992-1998; 1 folder (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Troupe, Margaret Porter and Quincy, 1989-2000; 1 folder (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Tubert, Susana, 2000-2010; 1 folder (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Unknown Sender, 2 folders (Box 97, Folder 1-2, Box 96, Folder 4-7)
  - Urban, Amanda "Binky", undated; 1 folder (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - V, 1970-2005; 1 folder (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Velasquez, Chloe, 1984-2015; 2 folders (Box 97, Folder 5-6)
    Toni Morrison's niece
  - Velasquez, Sage, 2006-2007; 1 folder (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Verdelle, A.J., 1995-2012; 1 folder (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Vereen, Ben, 1998-2000; 1 folder (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - W, 1970-2005; 2 folders (Box 98, Folder 1-2)
  - Wall, Cheryl, 1985-2012; 1 folder (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Walker, Alice, 1978-1995; 1 folder (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Walker, B.B., 1992-1997; 1 folder (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Walker, Joan and Lorenzo, 1980-2015; 3 folders (Box 98, Folder 6-8)
  - Wang, Anne, 1987-1988; 1 folder (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Wangerin, Walter, 1996-2008; 1 folder (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - West, Cornel, 1992, undated; 1 folder (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - White, Armond, 1997-2000; 1 folder (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - White, Marvina, 1992-2001; 1 folder (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Wiesel, Elie, 1993-2002; 1 folder (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Wilcox, Jim, 1985-1997; 1 folder (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Wilentz, Sean, 1993-1999; 1 folder (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Williams, C.K., 1998-2002; 1 folder (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Williams, John, 1985-1996; 1 folder (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Williams, Patricia J., 1998; 1 folder (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Williams, Sherley Anne, 1986; 1 folder (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Willis, Anne, 1978-2011; 1 folder (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Willis, Avery, 1987-2015; 1 folder (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Willis, Goreleigh, 1988-2012; 1 folder (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - Willis, Sr., John, 1982-1984; 1 folder (Box 99, Folder 13)
    Toni Morrison's uncle
  - Willis, John, 1986-1989; 1 folder (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - Willis, Saundra, 1993-2010; 1 folder (Box 99, Folder 15)
  - Wilson, Robert, 1999-2003; 1 folder (Box 99, Folder 16)
  - Winfrey, Oprah, 1990-2010; 2 folders (Box 99, Folder 17-18)
  - Winters, Heather, 2006-2008; 1 folder (Box 99, Folder 19)
  - Wofford, George, 1984-1989; 1 folder (Box 100, Folder 1)
    TM's brother
  - Wofford, Lois Yvonne Bell, 1996, 2000; 1 folder (Box 100, Folder 2)
    TM's niece
  - Wofford, Misha, 1992-2001; 1 folder (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Wofford, Ramah, 1977-1986; 1 folder (Box 100, Folder 4)
    TM's mother
  - Wofford, Raymond, 1988-1992; 1 folder (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Wofford, Tammara, 1993-2006; 1 folder (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Wolitzer, Hilma, 1987-1991; 1 folder (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Woods, Donnie, 1977-1988; 1 folder (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Woods, Joyce Ann, 1981-1992, undated; 1 folder (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Woods, Stephanie, 1994-2007; 1 folder (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - X, Y, Z, 1970-2005; 1 folder (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - Yoshida, Michiko, 1991-2003; 1 folder (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Zinsser, William, 1986; 1 folder (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - Screenplay Drafts, 1983; 4 folders Typescript, corrected. (Box 10, Folder 1-4, Box 11, Folder 1-2)
- Series 3: Random House, 1971-1982; 2 boxes
  Includes annotated typescript draft fragments of The Greatest by Muhammad Ali and Angela Davis: An Autobiography, in addition to correspondence, press releases, contracts, and press clippings related to these and other projects Morrison worked on while at Random House.
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  - Ali, Muhammad, 1973-1975; 1 folder (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Baldwin, James, 1973-1975; 1 folder (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - The Black Book, 1974-1978; 1 folder (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Chinweizu, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Cosby, Bill, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Davis, Angela, 1971-1973; 2 folders (Box 101, Folder 6-7)
  - Diamond, Stanley, 1975-1979; 1 folder (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Forrest, Leon, undated; 1 folder (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Lester, Julius, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - McPherson, James, 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1972-1978; 1 folder (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous MS Inquiries, 1977-1982; 1 folder (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - "Toni Morrison" Letterhead Stationery, undated; 1 folder (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Van Sertima, Ivan, 1971-1981; 4 folders (Box 102, Folder 4-7)
- Series 4: SUNY Albany, 1984-1989; 2 boxes
  This material is stored off site. Please allow 24-48 hrs for retrieval.
  - The Birth of Black Cinema, 1986-1988; 3 folders (Box 103, Folder 1-3)
  - Colia Clark Advisory Panel, 1986; 1 folder (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1985-1989; 1 folder (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - New York State Writer's Institute, 1984-1986; 1 folder (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Schweitzer Chair Program, 1984-1988; 1 folder (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Schweitzer DBASE Program Files, 1986; 1 folder (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Schweitzer Fellows, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Schweitzer Reports, 1985-1986; 2 folders (Box 104, Folder 3-4)
- Series 5: Princeton University, 1986-2011; 3 boxes
  - 110 Dickinson move to 185, 2002; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - 111 Dickinson move to 185, 2002; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - 185 Nassau St. Offices, 1994-2002; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - 250th Anniversary Committee, 1992-1997; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Administrative Memos, 1987-1997; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - African-American Studies Program, 1986-2002; 5 folders (Box 105, Folder 6-10)
  - Afro-American Studies Party: Simmons/TM Birthday, 1989-1993; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - African-American Studies Post-doc Program, 1990-1991; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - African-American Studies Post-docs: Fordham and Awkward, 1991; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - African-American Studies Post-doc Queries, 1991-1998; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - African-American Studies Search Committee, 1999-2000; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 15)
  - Alumni Council, 1989-2003; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 16)
  - American Studies/Anthropology, 1990-1997; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 17)
  - Articles about Princeton's Black Community, 1990-1995; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 18)
  - Athletics/Black Employees Association, 1987-1998; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 19)
  - Building/Furniture Info, 1990-1991; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 20)
  - Chapel, 1990-1998; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 21)
  - Center for Arts and Cultural Policy Studies, 1994-2002; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 22)
  - Center for Human Values, 1994-2004; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 23)
  - Center of International Studies/Institute for Transregional Study, 1995-2000; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 24)
  - Communications, 1987-2001; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 25)
  - Comparative Literature, 1997-1998; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 26)
  - Council of the Humanities, 1988-2010; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 27)
  - Creative Writing, 1987-2005; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 28)
  - Davis Center, 1990-1992; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 29)
  - Dean of the College, 1988-1996; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 30)
  - Dean of the Faculty, 1989-2001; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 31)
  - Development, 1989-2005; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 32)
  - English, 1988-2002; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 33)
  - Graduate College, 1992-1999; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 34)
  - History/Hellenic Studies, 1993-2003; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 35)
  - Homelessness Project, 1991-1992; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 36)
  - Humanities Council, 1989-1994; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 37)
  - Human Resources, 1992; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 38)
  - Library, Mathey College, Near Eastern Studies, 1993-2005; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 39)
  - Miscellaneous, 1987-2011; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 40)
  - Move to Dickinson, 1988-1990; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 41)
  - Moving Preparation, 2001-2002; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 42)
  - Office Hardware and Equipment, 1989-1992; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Office Supplies and Expenses, 1989-1991; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Politics, 1987-1997; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - President/Vice-President, 1989-2010; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Press, 1987-1997; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Program in Theater and Dance/Visual Arts, 1990-1994; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Provost, 1991-2003; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Religion, 1993-2001; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Romance Languages and Literature, 1989-1999; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Saunders, Ronnie, 1989-1992; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Sociology, 1993-1998; 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Tanner Committee, 1996-2001; 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Target of Opportunity Search Committee, 2002-2003; 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Toni Morrison Birthday-2/26/95, 1995; 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Toni Morrison Birthday Party-2/26/94, 1994; 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - Toni Morrison Party-10/17/93, 1993; 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Vice-President for Public Affairs, 1991-1993; 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Wallace Fellowship, 1989; 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - Women's Studies, 1989-1995; 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Women's Center/Third World Center/Center for Jewish Life/International Center, 1989-2002; 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - Woodrow Wilson School/Terrace Club, 1989-2000; 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 11)
- Series 6: Teaching Files, 1985-2009; 6 boxes
  - The American Self/Selves, 1989; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Art and Culture in Modern Afro-American Fiction, 1989-1991; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Atelier, 1992-2009; portions of 2 boxes
    - American Ballet Theatre, 1997-1999; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Anonymous 4, 2002-2003; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Binnerts, Paul and Christine Jones, 2002-2004; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Bodies in Evidence, 2006-2009; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Budgets, 1995-2004; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Danielpour, Richard, Yo Yo Ma, Edgar Meyer, and Toni Morrison, 1996; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - Danielpour, Richard and Toni Morrison, 2002-2003; 2 folders (Box 108, Folder 9-10)
    - Eckert, Rinde and Steve Mackey, 2003-2004; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - Fundraiser: Carpenter/Waletzky Dinner, 2000; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 12)
    - Fundraiser: Frelinghuysen Cocktail Party, 1997-1999; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 13)
    - Fundraising, 1997-2004; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 14)
    - Fundraising and Publicity Texts, 1996-2002; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 15)
    - Hagen, Daron and Paul Muldoon, 1998-2005; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 16)
    - Invitation Lists, 1997-2000; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 17)
    - Kahn, Nicholas and Richard Selesnick, 2002; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 18)
    - Kommunyakaa, Yusef, 2001-2002; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 19)
    - Lieberman, Erez, 2002; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 20)
    - Magnus, Erica, 2004-2005; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 21)
    - Manter, Nancy and Ben Shedd, 2001-2004; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 22)
    - Marquez, Gabriel Garcia, 1996-1998; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous, 1994-2005; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 24)
    - Modica, Andrea, 1999; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 25)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol and Susana Tubert, 1997-1999; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 26)
    - Obadike, Mendi and Keith, 2003-2005; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 27)
    - Olson, Sarah, 2005; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 28)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1997-2005; 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Pig Iron Theater, 2002-2003; 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Price, Richard, 2002-2003; 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Proposals, 1992-2008; 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Provost/Humanities Council, 1998-2005; 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Publicity, 1997; 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Reagon, Bernice Johnson, 1997; 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Sadovska, Mariana, Roger Babb, Lars Jan, 2004-2005; 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - Sanderson, Christopher, 2001; 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - Sellars, Peter, undated; 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - Tucci, Maria, Allegra Kent, Daniel Mendelsohn, 2004-2006; 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - Contemporary Black Women and Their Fiction, 1985; 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 12)
  - Creative Writing, 1985-1994; 2 folders
    - Annotated Readings, undated; 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 13)
    - Exercises, 1990-1994; portion of 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 14)
    - Syllabi, Schedules, Etc., 1985-1994; portion of 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 14)
  - The Foreigner's Home: Studies in the Literature of Dispossession, 2007-2009; 2 folders (Box 109, Folder 16-17)
  - Global Fiction, 1998; 2 folders (Box 109, Folder 18-19)
  - On Morrison: The Literary Imagination, 1997; 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 20)
  - Studies in American Africanism, 1987-1996; 3 boxes (2 partial)
    - Annotated Bibliography, undated; 2 folders (Box 109, Folder 21-22)
    - Annotated Readings, undated; 2 folders (Box 109, Folder 23-24)
    - Aunt Jemima Advertising and Identity, undated; 1 folder (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Book Orders/Library Reserve, 1989-1996; 2 folders (Box 110, Folder 2-3)
    - Class Lists, 1989-1996; 1 folder (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Course Reader, 1992; 1 folder (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Course Reader, 1996; 1 folder (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Lecture: "The Matter of Africanism", circa 1989-1996; 1 folder (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Lecture: "Shadow and Flight", circa 1989-1996; 2 folders (Box 110, Folder 8-9)
    - Lecture: "Surrogate Self as Enabler", circa 1989-1996; 1 folder (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - Lecture: William Styron, circa 1989-1996; 1 folder (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - Lecture: "Text and Context: Uncle Tom's Cabin", circa 1989-1996; 1 folder (Box 110, Folder 12)
    - Lecture: Mark Twain, circa 1989-1996; 1 folder (Box 110, Folder 13)
    - Lecture: Gertrude Stein, circa 1989-1996; 1 folder (Box 110, Folder 14)
    - Lecture: William Faulker, circa 1989-1996; 2 folders (Box 110, Folder 15-16)
    - Lecture: "Bellow: Henderson the Rain King", circa 1989-1996; 1 folder (Box 110, Folder 17)
    - Lecture: "O'Connor and McCullers: Surrogate Enablers", circa 1989-1996; 1 folder (Box 110, Folder 18)
    - Lecture: "Willa Cather: The Fugitive(s) Plot", circa 1989-1996; 1 folder (Box 110, Folder 19)
    - Lectures, circa 1991-1993; 2 folders (Box 111, Folder 1-2, Box 110, Folder 20)
    - Manuscript, 1993; 2 folders (Box 111, Folder 3-4)
      With correspondence from Peter Dimock.
    - Miscellaneous Lecture Material, circa 1989-1996; 2 folders (Box 110, Folder 5-6)
      See also Playing in the Dark
    - McBride, Dwight, 1989; 1 folder (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - McGowan, Tara, 1990-1993; 1 folder (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Memos, 1989-1996; 1 folder (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - Precepts/Preceptors, 1991-1996; 1 folder (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - Racial Matters in Media, 1990; 1 folder (Box 111, Folder 11)
    - Slides, 1989; 1 folder (Box 111, Folder 12)
    - Study Questions and Paper Topics, 1989-1996; 1 folder (Box 111, Folder 13)
    - Syllabi and Bibliographies, 1989-1996; 3 folders (Box 111, Folder 14-16)
    - Third World View of Western Canon, 1987-1988; 1 folder (Box 111, Folder 17)
    - Various Working Materials, circa 1989-1996; 2 folders (Box 111, Folder 18-19)
  - Unidentified Class and Lecture Notes, undated; 1 folder (Box 111, Folder 20)
  - Student Progress Notes, 1990 Spring; 1 folder (Box 112, Folder 1)
    This material is closed until 2084.
  - Class Record Books, 1989-1998; 5 folders (Box 112, Folder 2-6)
  - Atelier Student Critiques, 2005-2009; 2 folders (Box 112, Folder 7-8)
  - Course Evaluations, 1989-1996; 2 folders (Box 112, Folder 9-10)
  - Grades and Critiques, 1989-2009; 3 folders (Box 112, Folder 11-13)
  - Student Papers, 1989-2009; 15 folders (Box 114, Folder 1-15, Box 113, Folder 1-12, Box 112, Folder 14-16)
    Arranged alphabetically by the student's last name.
- Series 7: Photographs, 1940-2012; more than 9 boxes (1 partial)
  - Promotional Headshots and Portraits, 1970-2003; portions of more than 2 boxes
    - Holt, Rinehart, and Winston Bluest Eye Author Photo, circa 1970; Andrews, Bert; 1 folder (Box Photos 1, Folder 1)
      6 photographs, black and white. 1 signed by Morrison.
    - Knopf Sula Author Photos, circa 1973; Cream, Bob; 1 folder (Box Photos 1, Folder 2)
      11 photographs, black and white.
    - Knopf Tar Baby Author Photo, 1981; Victor, Thomas; 1 folder (Box Photos 1, Folder 3)
      3 photographs, black and white.
    - Knopf Beloved Author Photo, circa 1987; Greenfield-Sanders, Timothy; 1 folder (Box Photos 1, Folder 4)
      3 photographs and contact sheet, black and white.
    - Knopf Jazz and Paradise Author Photo, undated; Kunz, Kate; 1 folder (Box Photos 1, Folder 5)
      8 photographs, black and white.
    - Knopf Jazz and Playing in the Dark Author Photos, 1989-1993; Lanker, Brian; 1 folder (Box Photos 1, Folder 6)
      10 photographs, black and white. With Jazz publicity cards and note from Knopf Promotion Department.
    - Who's Got Game? Series Promo Shots, circa 2003; 1 folder (Box Photos 1, Folder 7)
      3 printouts, color. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Slade Morrison.
    - University Relations Photos, SUNY Albany, circa 1987; Hoy, Ray; 1 folder (Box Photos 7, Folder 1)
      10 black and white photographs; 4 contact sheets; note from the Office of the President, SUNY Albany. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Vincent O'Leary.
    - Schweitzer Chair Publicity Photo, 1985; Marcus, Helen; 1 folder (Box Photos 1, Folder 9)
      3 photographs, black and white; negative; letter from Nicholas Latimer at Knopf.
    - Princeton Development Communications Photos, circa 1997; 1 folder (Box Photos 1, Folder 18)
      29 photographs, 2 contact sheets, and letter from Princeton Development Communications Office.
    - Headshots, undated; Crampton, Nancy; 1 folder (Box Photos 1, Folder 8)
      2 printouts; 1 black and white, 1 color.
    - Portrait, undated; Colita; 1 folder (Box Photos 1, Folder 10)
      1 photograph, black and white; with note from "B" at The New Yorker.
    - Portraits, undated; Mulas, Maria; 1 folder (Box Photos 1, Folder 11)
      6 photographs, black and white. Pictured: Toni Morrison, James Baldwin.
    - Portrait, undated; Gotfryd, Bernard; 1 folder (Box Photos 1, Folder 12)
      1 proof, black and white.
    - Portrait, undated; Greenfield-Sanders, Timothy; 1 folder (Box Photos 1, Folder 13)
      1 printout, color.
    - Portraits, undated; Giovannetti, Giovanni; 1 folder (Box Photos 1, Folder 14)
      11 photographs. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Carla Tanzi.
    - Portrait, Black Oak Books, Berkeley, 1987; Koolish, Lynda; 1 folder (Box Photos 1, Folder 15)
      1 photograph, black and white; exhibition announcement and letter from Lynda Koolish, dated 2001.
    - Toni Morrison in Paris, Hôtel des Saints-Pères, 1985 January; Regnault, Chantal; 1 folder (Box Photos 1, Folder 16)
      1 photograph, black and white; postcard from Chantal Regnault.
    - Toni Morrison and Angela Davis, New York City, 1974; Krementz, Jill; 1 folder (Box Photos 1, Folder 17)
      3 photocopies, black and white.
    - NYPL Campaign News Photo, 1987 October; 1 folder (Box Photos 1, Folder 19)
      1 photograph, black and white; letter from Jennifer Herring, Deputy Director, Campaign for the Library. Pictured: Toni Morrison and Liz Rohatyn.
    - Assorted Portraits, undated; 5 folders (Box Photos 1, Folder 20-24)
  - Awards, Lectures, and Events, 1980-2011; more than 9 boxes (3 partial)
    - Harvard University Commencement, 1989; 1 folder (Box Photos 1, Folder 25)
      16 photographs, black and white; letter from Richard M. Hunt, University Marshal.
    - Spelman College Reading, 1990 November 15; Ross, Susan J.; 1 folder (Box Photos 1, Folder 26)
      Approximately 90 photographs, black and white and color; promotional notice for lecture and Susan J. Ross photocopied business card.
    - Syracuse University Visiting Professor, 1988 October 5-26; 1 folder (Box Photos 2, Folder 1)
      42 black and white photographs; 6 color photographs; press release and clippings.
    - Pell Awards, 2001 April 27; Meyers, John; 1 folder (Box Photos 2, Folder 2)
      2 color photographs, 1 black and white photograph, note from Chira DelSesto.
    - Ruth Simmons Inauguration, Smith College, 1995 October; 1 folder (Box Photos 2, Folder 3)
      21 color photographs.
    - An Evening with Toni Morrison and Her Friends, St. John's Cathedral, 1994 April 5; 1 folder (Box Photos 2, Folder 4)
      6 color photographs. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Harry Belafonte, Bill Cosby.
    - TIME 75th Anniversary Gala, 1998 March 3; McMullan, Patrick; 1 folder (Box Photos 2, Folder 5)
      1 color photograph, commemorative program, and note from Patrick McMullan.
    - Negro Ensemble Co. Party, 1982; Andrews, Bert; 1 folder (Box Photos 2, Folder 6)
      1 black and white photograph; letter from Edward Burbridge dated March 30 1998. Pictured: Clinton Turner David, Lauren Jones, Jackee, Toni Morrison, Edward Burbridge, Billie Allen Henderson.
    - Bicentennial of the Library of Congress Tea, 1997 October 7; 1 folder (Box Photos 2, Folder 7)
      2 color photographs and letter from White House Social Secretary. Pictured: Toni Morrison and Hillary Clinton.
    - Tribeca Film Festival Dinner, 2002 May 7; 1 folder (Box Photos 2, Folder 8)
      1 color photograph and card from Graydon Carter.
    - Melcher Book Award, circa 1988; Kemp, Lilian; 1 folder (Box Photos 2, Folder 9)
      1 black and white photograph.
    - Follow Me Home Screening Afterparty, 1996; Freeman, Roland L.; 1 folder (Box Photos 2, Folder 10)
      3 black and white photographs. Featuring: Toni Morrison, June Jordan, Peter Bratt, Benjamin Bratt.
    - Langston Hughes Festival Award Gala, City College of New York, 1986 March 23; 1 folder (Box Photos 2, Folder 11)
      1 color photograph and letter from Raymond Patterson, Langston Hughes Committee.
    - Song of Solomon Oprah Book Club, 1996; 1 folder (Box Photos 2, Folder 12)
      1 color photograph; letter from Olivia Gerth, Associate Producer, Oprah Winfrey Show.
    - David Rockefeller Nelson Mandela Dinner, 1993 July 5; 1 folder (Box Photos 2, Folder 13)
      3 color photographs; letter from David Rockefeller.
    - University of Michigan Commencement, 1992; 1 folder (Box Photos 2, Folder 14)
      8 color photographs; notecard from James J. Duderstadt. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Joyce Carol Oates.
    - Reading from Paradise, Smith College, 1995 September 30; 1 folder (Box Photos 2, Folder 15)
      1 color photograph.
    - Borders/National Book Foundation Event, circa 1997; Wagner International.; 1 folder (Box Photos 2, Folder 16)
      10 color photographs.
    - Dartmouth College Montgomery Fellowship, 1982; 1 folder (Box Photos 2, Folder 17)
      7 black and white photographs.
    - Dartmouth College Montgomery Fellowship, 1986 July; 1 folder (Box Photos 2, Folder 18)